hi so this is one of the companies uh
which i tweeted last
week over the weekend of uh which i
am looking into and one of the
very interesting stuff which we can see
is
that it's particularly a range mount
since uh last december it's toggling
between 15 30 40
and 1400 and 1420
so it has been in this range it tried to
give a breakout but
it failed miserably and after that it
again
immediately came back in this room range
and it has been
consolidating since so here you can see
there are multiple instances
where this level was tested and we
tested and we tested
and again there was a retest happening
and right now it's over here at a 15 15
levels and it
might again go for a re-test over here
and similarly from a support point of
view
there were multiple instances we can see
it's a 3 over here
and it's a 4 over here and 5
6. so there has been a multiple and even
in this particular run there was a
support and right now it's
increase right now is heading towards
the upper range
going forward i think uh this would be
uh one of the bigger
trades that would be interesting for me
uh i would be very much
interested in if you look into a hourly
chart say for example
and here you will see that any hourly
closing above this
1550 region followed by
uh if there is no follow-up selling
and then this can actually lead to its
all-time high
towards a 1620 so that would um
corresponds to some 70 point which
should be
five four to five percent for this
particular script
and this is exactly what i'm eyeing for
uh short term
of course i'll be uh they're gonna say
your company here i see i say lombard
or the insurance center company
[Music]
for a new breakout given the sentiment
of the market
and given the particular way the script
is working again 1550 regions
uh 30 so i can easily see 1650
as your immediate target this would be a
new all-time high
and this would be one of the targets i
would be achieving thanks a lot for
listening let's see
here maybe a 1550 region
correct okay it was 1480 yeah 1440
but i think maybe
[Music]
so we can easily forget this it's not so
important
since august of uh 2019
yeah it's a trend line both my newly
followed
it has been through as an all-time high
happy eye it has gone for all-time high
and
i expect it to be touching around about
at least 1650 and at best 1700.
the good thing which i can say is it has
been in a range and there has been a lot
of consolidation
uh so i think this time it would be a
breakout
and if this breakout happens i think one
of the things
which would happen is
uh this will immediately have a very
powerful momentum run
or harm us metrics
always have these in your tracker this
is one of a very good companies
so if you look for a monthly
so you can see it was always in an
uptrend downfall joby i
they always got bought and they were all
only short term
and eventually this company is poised to
give much higher returns in the long
run thanks a lot for listening i hope
this was helpful